> > Jem Young: 我们再来一次练习。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So
let's try another exercise.
我们试试追踪路线
Let's try trace routes.
我喜欢跟踪路线
I love trace routes.
所以每当我放人的时候都是为了你自己的信息
So whenever I put man something,
that's just for your own information.
你知道我不仅仅是给你随机的命令
Just so you know that I'm not
just giving you random commands,
这才是今天的事
cuz that's what this day's all about.
我想让你知道我们在做什么
I want you to have context
on what we're doing.
我们今天学到的很多，您可以从教程或
A lot of what we learn today,
you can learn from a tutorial or
你可以在谷歌上或者类似的地方查查看
you can look it up on Google or
something like that.
但我想给你所有背景让你问问题
But I wanna give you all the context and
allow you to ask questions and
不能只输入任意命令。
not just type in arbitrary commands.
因此，如果您想运行 traceroute ，请仅运行 traceroute google.com。
So if you wanna run traceroute,
just run traceroute google.com.
我会在这里做的
And I'll go ahead and do that here.
清除google.com 。
Clear, google.com.
当然，我想让你看起来很酷。
And of course, the side benefits classes,
I wanna make you look cool.
所以如果你只是在电脑里想讨好别人
So if you're just at a computer and
trying to impress someone,
只会让 traceroute 发生什么事
just run traceroute something.
它让它看起来像你在做这些很酷的事情。
And it makes it look like you're
doing all this really cool stuff.
但是我们真正做的不是 ping ，而是直接用于这个，
But all we're really doing is instead
of ping, which goes directly to this,
它击中了一个回来的服务器说我还活着
it hits a server that comes back and
says, hey, I'm alive.
Traceroute 为您提供了一个沿该点的地图。
Traceroute gives you a map of
every single hop along that point.
记住我是怎么说互联网建立在服务器和节点上的信任
Remember, how I said the Internet's
built on trust in servers, and nodes,
还有开关吗
and switches?
这就是我们要做的
That's what we're doing.
它映射了每一个我们点击的服务器的路径。
It's mapping the path of every single
server that we hit along the way.
所以每次你看一跳，跳一到二，两到三，
So every time you see another hop, and a
hop is just from one to two, two to three,
三到四种之类的东西
three to four stuff like that.
上面说我在 192.168.3.1
It just says, hey, I'm at 192.168.3.1.
我想去 172.2178.174
I'm trying to get to 172.217.8.174.
我怎么才能到那儿
How do I get there?
所以每一个跳服务器都是这样的，我不知道，但这个人知道。
So every single hop the server's like,
I don't know, but this person knows.
我不知道但这个人知道
最终它就会被传递到一起
And eventually it just gets passed along,
passed along,
直到我们最终在这里真正的谷歌服务器上结束
passed until we end up on the actual
Google server, which is here.
我喜欢 traceroute cuz ，它让我看起来很酷。
I love traceroute cuz, one,
it makes me look cool.
第二，它帮助诊断网络问题。
Two, it helps diagnose network problems.
那么，如果你有一个网站，你的客户说，哎，
So again, if you have a website and
your client says, hey,
我无法到达你的网站你可以运行 traceroute
I can't reach your website,
you can run traceroute.
而 traceroute 会告诉你如果你无法连接的话
And traceroute will tell you exactly where
the hops break down if you can't connect
也可以到现场
to the site either.
所以它可能是一百九十二个，一般都是，
So it could be a hit here which
will be 192, it's generally,
.168 几乎是本地网络。
.168 is your local network almost always.
而这里的点击率是，同流派的人说的，是 ISP吗 ?
And it hits here,
cogento cogento said that, is that an ISP?
不知道，国家的不同部分，但这也打击了 ISP 和
Didn't know, different part of the
country, but that's hitting the ISP and
这就是试图解决的问题 -- > 演讲者 2: 摄政王是我们的 ISP。
that's trying to resolve-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Cogent is our ISP.
>> Jem Young: Cogentco， [SOUND] cogentco，这是一个好名字。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Cogentco,
[SOUND] cogentco, that's a good name.
好吧，但是基本上，让我们说两个人在这里死了。
All right, but essentially, let's say
the hops died here at number two.
这意味着 ISP 不能解决问题，而且你知道一些事情是一般的。
That means the ISP is not resolving, and
you know something's just out in general.
如果我们再下去我们就更接近谷歌的分解员了
Versus if we get further down,
we get closer to the Google resolver,
当我们接近实际服务器时它就会消失
as we get closer and closer to
the actual server, and it dies out.
我们知道它可能是一个负载均衡器，它可能是谷歌本身。
We know that it could be a load balancer
that's out, it's probably Google itself.
跟踪路由对
Trace route is very useful for
如果你想确定你的网站出了什么问题
that if you're trying to determine
what's wrong with your site.
这就是你的背口袋里的东西
Again, it's just this thing
to have in your back pocket.
举个例子，当我在家的时候，跳得更快。
And an example of, when I did it at home,
it was much faster hops.
实际上，有 16 个希望能到达谷歌，这其实挺有希望的。
There's actually 16 hops to get to Google,
which is actually quite a bit.
他们通常是非常非常快的
They're usually really, really fast.
请在 frontendmasters.com上试用 traceroute 。
So try traceroute on frontendmasters.com.
>> Jem Young: traceroute。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: traceroute.
>> Jem Young: 也许，也许会解决问题。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Maybe,
maybe it will resolve.
上次我试过这个也没解决
When I tried this last time,
it didn't resolve.
现在可以解决了
It may resolve now.
但发生了什么我就把它开过去换过去
But what's happening,
I'll just leave it running, switch over.
正在发生的是 traceroute 和
What's happening is traceroute and
ping 操作都在运行称为 ICMP 请求的事件。
ping are both running
a thing called ICMP requests.
所以 ICMP 是互联网控制报文协议而不是 TCP
So ICMP is Internet Control
Message Protocol, instead of TCP,
就是传输控制协议
which is Transmission Control Protocol.
这是说，嘿，这些是健康检查。
This is saying, hey,
these are health checks of sort.
所以 ping 是一种健康检查，说你还活着吗 ?
So ping is a sort of health check saying,
are you alive?
Traceroute ，它需要多少跳才能到达服务器，你还活着吗 ?
Traceroute is, how many hops does it take
to get to the server, are you alive?
看起来像是
And looks like it,
您可以将服务器配置为根本不响应 ICMP 请求。
you can configure your server to not
respond to ICMP requests at all.
如果你想 ping frontendmasters.com也会发生同样的事
So the same thing happens if you
try to ping frontendmasters.com,
它不会响应的
it won't respond.
这就是我们所谓的 " 黑洞 " 。
And this is what is we call black holing.
如果你想明确拒绝请求你可以说不允许
Where, if you wanna explicitly deny
requests, you can say, not allowed,
别这样别这样
hey, don't do that.
我们不会接受的
We're not gonna accept that.
黑洞刚说我们都不会回应你的要求
Black holing is just saying, we're not
even gonna respond to your requests.
如果你有个派对你会看到一个很酷的人
If you had a party and
you see a cool person and
他们就完全不理你了
they just ignore you completely.
那是个黑色的洞
That's kinda black holing.
从没发生过这种事
That never happens to me, ever.
我是派对上的凉爽的人
I was the cool person at the party.
我们今天分享了很多信息我们有很长的路要走
We're sharing a lot of information today,
[LAUGH] we got a long way.
我们会在最后的过程中相互了解
We're gonna get to know
each other by the end.
所以 frontendmasters.com 它配置的方式就是把他们的
So frontendmasters.com, the way it's
configured is they just set their
ICMP 请求到一个，他们就会忽略所有这些请求。
ICMP requests to one,
they're just gonna ignore all of them.
这就是 ping 和 traceroute 不起作用的原因。
And that's why ping and
traceroute don't work.
您可以配置 Web 站点以执行该操作。
You can configure your website to do that.
也许你不想被人判死刑通常不会再发生了
Maybe you don't wanna get pinged to death,
which usually doesn't happen anymore.
但在互联网的旧日里，你可以通过 ping 他们的方式来获取网站。
But in the old days of the Internet, you
could take down a site by pinging them.
我可以设置 5 台或 6 台服务器并保持 ping， ping， ping 和
I can set up five or six servers and
just keep pinging, pinging, pinging, and
因为每一个 ping ，计算机都有义务对你做出回应。
because every ping, the computer
is obligated to respond to you.
你可以先去个网站
You can take down a website before,
现在是旧日了，现在不行了。
this is the old days,
now it won't work anymore.
但它只会让服务器过载。
But it would just overload
the server with requests.
您可能要对您的服务器禁用该设置，您可能不希望这样做。
And you may wanna disable that for
your server, you might not want to.
我通常会活的
I usually keep it alive.
它有利于调试，所以我可以 ping 自己的网站。
It's good for debugging, so
I can ping my own website.
我可以在它上运行 traceroute ，但有时你不想要。
I can run traceroute on it, but
sometimes you don't want that.
这对你来说很重要，那就是运行自己的服务器的伟大之处，
And that's totally up to you, that's the
great thing about running your own server,
你是否有完全的控制
is you have complete control.